doujinmode.net 2016-06-29

# Privacy Policy | TOKYO DOUJIN MODE

statement below outlines the DoujinMode.net website ("Tokyo Doujin Mode") Privacy Policy. Tokyo Doujin Mode may update its Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the products and services that Tokyo Doujin Mode offers, however, the underlying goal of protecting user privacy remains the same. By using Tokyo Doujin Mode's service, each user consents to the collection, use or disclosure of their Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Tokyo Doujin Mode service following the "last-revised" date on this Privacy Policy will represent your consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information under this Privacy Policy as modified. You are advised to review this page regularly for any changes.users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, or feel that Tokyo Doujin Mode has not complied with the Policy, they should first contact [https://goo.gl/C6Xp4h](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1v2z1IdbUf2Wq5a174AN-iuRSNuB4V_mddjaKmWWm048/viewform).

## STORAGE AND USE OF USER INFORMATION

Doujin Mode stores information as described below that could be used to identify users ("Personal Information") on the Tokyo Doujin Mode servers for the sole purpose of providing the Tokyo Doujin Mode service to users. Tokyo Doujin Mode also stores certain non-personally identifiable information using log files.following paragraph describes the Personal Information collected on Tokyo Doujin Mode servers: email address, name and mailing address, telephone number, payment and usage records.

## COMMUNICATIONS FROM THE SITE

## UPDATES AND NOTIFICATIONS

email address of account holder is used for confirmation of a successful account creation. Account holders can opt out from the updates at any time by logging into their account to modify their update preference. Users also have the right to opt in or opt out of communications related to such services as, but not limited to, new application launches, promotions, Tokyo Doujin Mode contests and events. Tokyo Doujin Mode may also collect the account holder's cell phone number if the account holder opts in to an SMS alert service.

## SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENTS

rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if the service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, Tokyo Doujin Mode might send users an email or SMS message. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

## CUSTOMER SERVICE

Doujin Mode communicates with users on a regular basis to provide requested services. In regards to issues relating to their account, Tokyo Doujin Mode replies via email or phone, in accordance with the user's wishes.

## SURVEYS

, Tokyo Doujin Mode' site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose information. The requested information typically includes marketing or product feedback information and, in some cases, optional contact and / or demographic information. If provided, contact information may be used for testimonials or to request additional feedback information. Users will be advised and given an opportunity to consent or opt-out of such uses. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Tokyo Doujin Mode website and Tokyo Doujin Mode service. Users' Personal Information is not shared with third parties unless Tokyo Doujin Mode provides prior notice and the choice to users. Though Tokyo Doujin Mode may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, the intermediary may not use users' Personal Information for any secondary purposes.

## ELIGIBILITY

Doujin Mode does not intentionally collect or use personal information about individuals under the age of 13. Consequently, use of this web and mobile internet site and all related services by children under the age of 13 is strictly prohibited. Tokyo Doujin Mode reserves the right to delete, move, edit, refuse to post or take other appropriate action with respect to any messages, information or files which Tokyo Doujin Mode, in its sole discretion, deems objectionable or otherwise in violation of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.

## COOKIES

cookie is a piece of data stored on the users' computer or cellular phone tied to information about the user. Tokyo Doujin Mode uses session ID cookies. However, the user must opt-in to the usage of cookies by indicating that their login credentials be remembered when they login in subsequent sessions. Tokyo Doujin Mode may also use cookies that are not linked to any Personal Information to store certain preferences about the user's use of the services. For example, cookies may be used to allow a user to set a preference to skip a verification screen when capturing information.

## AGGREGATE INFORMATION

Doujin Mode may use users' Personal Information to generate aggregated information that does not allow the user to be personally identified or contacted. Aggregated Information shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis and may be used by Tokyo Doujin Mode to provide insight on the usage of the Tokyo Doujin Mode services.Doujin Mode allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

## WEB AND MOBILE INTERNET SITE ACTIVITY

most standard Web and mobile internet sites, Tokyo Doujin Mode stores and uses web server log files. These files include anonymous information about web browsers, such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Such log files are not linked to Personal Information through the Tokyo Doujin Mode service.

## SHARING

Doujin Mode will not share any information provided by users, except as follows:Information (non-personally identifiable)Doujin Mode may use users' Personal Information to generate aggregated information relating to activity on Tokyo Doujin Mode-enabled products and services. This aggregate information does not allow the user to be personally identified or contacted and shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis. This information is shared with relevant Tokyo Doujin Mode customers and partners.Tokyo Doujin Mode Discloses User InformationDoujin Mode may share users' Personal Information with its affiliates, subsidiaries and service providers for the sole purpose of providing the Tokyo Doujin Mode service to the user, provided that the information is required for and used only for such purpose and provided the information is used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Tokyo Doujin Mode will otherwise only release Personal Information to third parties in the following limited circumstances: (i) if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order legally requires Tokyo Doujin Mode to do so; (ii) if Tokyo Doujin Mode's rights or property or the rights or property of Tokyo Doujin Mode's affiliates, subsidiaries, service providers or the users of Tokyo Doujin Mode's web site or services are in jeopardy; or (iii) if the personal safety of users of Tokyo Doujin Mode's web site or services or other members of the public is in jeopardy.Transitionsthe event Tokyo Doujin Mode goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' Personal Information will, in most instances, be one of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email prior to a change of ownership or control of their Personal Information. If, as a result of the business transition, the users' Personal Information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, users will be given a choice to decline such different use.

## LINKS

Web or mobile internet site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tokyo Doujin Mode is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Tokyo Doujin Mode encourages its users to be aware when they leave the Tokyo Doujin Mode site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects Personal Information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Tokyo Doujin Mode web and internet mobile site.

## SECURITY

Doujin Mode employs security measures in order to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, theft and alteration of Personal Information under Tokyo Doujin Mode's control. However, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Consequently, Tokyo Doujin Mode, its affiliates, subsidiaries, service providers and their respective officers, directors, employees and agents do not represent, warrant or guarantee that Personal Information will be protected against misuse, loss or alterations and do not accept any liability for Personal Information submitted to or collected by them nor for your or third parties' use or misuse of Personal Information.

## CORRECTING/UPDATING/DELETING/DEACTIVATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

a user's Personal Information changes (such as phone, email address or cellular phone number), the user may update this information on the Tokyo Doujin Mode website or on their cellular phone. If a user no longer desires to use Tokyo Doujin Mode's service, Tokyo Doujin Mode provides a way to delete/deactivate users' Personal Information. Account deletion/deactivation can be done online http://doujinmode.net/

## NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

Tokyo Doujin Mode decide to change its privacy policy, changes to this privacy statement will be posted on the Tokyo Doujin Mode web site.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

users have any questions or suggestions regarding Tokyo Doujin Mode's privacy policy, or wish to obtain information on how to access their personal information held by Tokyo Doujin Mode, please contact Tokyo Doujin Mode at: [https://goo.gl/C6Xp4h](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1v2z1IdbUf2Wq5a174AN-iuRSNuB4V_mddjaKmWWm048/viewform)Revised Date: Nov 25, 2015
